Guide to the Donald Ogden Stewart and Ella Winter Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1915-1975; Series II; 37.42 linear feet (38 boxes)
  - Writings of Others
    - Gonzalez, J. J. "Jehovah and Grapes" draft, typescript, corrections (Box 52)
    - Gurova, A. "Working Women in Soviet People's War of Liberation" typed draft, undated (Box 52)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, [On Writing], typescript, with related ALS, (photocopy), 1924 (Box 52)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, "A note on Luis Quintanilla," typescript, 1943 (Box 52)
    - Ibsen, Henrick, "An Enemy of the People," adapted by Arthur Miller, typescript, 1950 (Box 52)
    - Keltisnleaya, Vera, "A Mother's Story" typed draft, undated (Box 52)
    - Lewis, Sinclair, "Cass Timberlane. A Preview. First and Second Reports," typescript, 1947 (Box 52)
    - McKechney, Donald, "The Devil's Strip," typescript, undated (Box 52)
    - Ogden, John, "Fourth of July in a Southern Prison," ms., undated (Box 52)
    - Oppenheimer, George, "The Lady and the Legend: A Memory of Dorothy Parker" typed draft, corrected, undated (Box 52)
    - Platt, David, "The Hollywood Witchunt of 1947," printed version, 1977 December
    - Smith, Lorna D. "People You Should Know: Donald Ogden Stewart," typed rough draft (Box 52)
    - Stewart, Gilbert Holland, "Anecdotes, legal and otherwise," 2 notebooks, undated (Box 52)
    - Stewart, Gilbert Holland, "The Capture, Imprisonment, Escape and Recapture of Lt. John Ogden," ms., 1877; 9 (Box 52)
    - _, Alex, "Neill" typed draft, 1962 (Box 52)
    - Unidentified, "A Parody Outline of History by Donald Ogden Stewart," review, typescript, undated (Box 52)
    - Various, undated (Box 52)
- Personal Papers, 1881-1976; Series III; 9.42 linear feet (10 boxes)
  Arranged alphabetically by name.
  The Personal Papers series contains diaries, journals, notebooks, scrapbooks, printed material, ephemera, photographs, and other material relating to the personal lives of Donald Ogden Stewart, Ella Winter, and their families. Documents in the series record Stewart and Winter's education, activities, and interests. The photographs, both snapshots and formal portraits, are a window into the everyday life, travels, and personal relationships of Stewart, Winter, their friends, and family.
  - Mitchell, Joseph, last will and testament, 1881 (Box 53)
  - Steffens, Lincoln, 1883-1906, undated
    - Diplomas, honor rolls, documents, 1906; undated
    - Drawing of Lincoln Steffens, undated
  - Steffens, Pete
    - Papers, 1943; undated; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - School papers, undated; 3 (Box 53)
  - Stewart, Alonzo, documents, 1839; 1846; undated (Box 53)
  - Stewart, Ames Ogden
    - Essays, 1949 May 31 (Box 53)
    - School reports, 1938; undated (Box 53)
    - Clipping, report cards, correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 53)
    - Drafts, ms. typescript, holograph, 1949-1953 (Box 53)
    - Advice on writing, 1953 November (Box 53)
    - Correspondence re: jobs, 1953-1956 (Box 53)
    - Resumes, 1956 (Box 53)
    - Income tax records, 1956-1957 (Box 53)
    - Savings account book, 1971-1976 (Box 53)
  - Tolstoy, Beatrice Ames, passport, 1924 (Box 53)
  - Stewart, Clara Ogden, calendar, 1928 (Box 53)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden
    - Grammar School and Sunday School memorabilia, undated (Box 53)
    - The Phillips Exeter Academy: memorabilia, 1911-1912 (Box 53)
    - Address book, passport, dance cards, 1911-1924 (Box 53)
    - Ephemera, 1899 (Box 53)
    - Documents, certificates and other papers, 1909-1940 (Box 53)
    - List of publications, undated; 2 (Box 53)
    - Card with drawing, undated (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous personal papers, 1911-1937 (Box 53)
    - Yale memorabilia, 1915-1921 (Box 53)
    - Photographs, undated; 2 (Box 53)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1912-1920; 6 (Box 53)
    - Yearbooks, 1912-1915; 2 (Box 54)
    - Scrapbook, 1884-1912
    - Scrapbook, 1887 (Box 54)
    - Scrapbook, 1913; undated
    - Posters for Congrès Mondial des Partisans de la Paix, 1949 April
    - High School and college diplomas, 1912 June 24-1916
    - World War I scrapbook, 1914-1918
    - Screen Writers Guild Annual Dinner Dance program, 1940 October 31 (Box 55)
    - Clippings, notes, undated; 5 (Box 55)
    - Clippings, notes, undated; 5 (Box 55)
    - Manuscripts, correspondence, clippings, 1916; undated (Box 55)
    - Bibles, 1850; 1852 (Box 55)
    - Yale notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 55)
    - Diary, 1909 October 31-1910 April 17 (Box 55)
    - Paris day planner, 1920s (Box 55)
    - Wedding invitation, 1928 June 23 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence, photographs, clippings, 1916; undated (Box 55)
    - Correspondence, 1916; 1934 (Box 55)
    - Yale College Exams, 1913 November 6-1916 Jan-Feb (Box 55)
    - Clippings, Photos, 1930; 1945 (Box 55)
    - Prayer books, 1927; undated (Box 55)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 55)
    - Pamphlets, undated; 4 (Box 55)
    - Notes, undated (Box 55)
    - Untitled ms., clippings, pamphlets, card written by young Stewart to parents, notes, 1901-1916 (Box 55)
    - Receipts, course of Study book, Yale College, exam, correspondence, expense book, clippings, 1914-1916 (Box 55)
    - Theatre programs, orchestra programs, catalogue, Yale Literary Magazine, clippings, miscellaneous, 1916-1919,undated (Box 55)
    - Correspondence, notes, and memorabilia, 1915-1916 (Box 56)
    - Publishers account, theatre programs, play book, correspondence, 1912-1925 (Box 56)
    - Clippings, ticket stubs, Theatre programs, 1912-1916 (Box 56)
    - Orchestra programs, untitled ms., Vassar College newsletter, clippings, correspondence, notes, 1912-1916 (Box 56)
    - Notes and clippings, 1878, undated (Box 56)
    - Enlistment paper, 1915 October 29 (Box 56)
    - Yale College rule book, address book, notes, postcards, Directory of Yale members of 1916, 1912-1916 (Box 56)
    - Programs, booklets, and correspondence, 1913-1918, undated (Box 56)
    - Phillips Exeter book, 1911 (Box 56)
    - Phillips Exeter class day booklets, 1912-1913 (Box 56)
    - Prayer books and notebook, undated (Box 56)
    - Cub Scout book, 1936 (Box 56)
    - Yale News, 1913-1915 (Box 56)
    - Yale News, Yale Alumni Weekly, college newspapers, 1978, 1913-1915 May 28 (Box 56)
    - Theatre programs and ad books, 1913-1914, undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Yale directory, exam, Yale Boat Club, Yale Record Banquet, 1913 (Box 56)
    - Railroad books, programs, clippings, 1915-1921, undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Cards, undated (Box 56)
    - Pamphlet, programs, ad book, booze book, 1910-1923; 2 (Box 56)
    - Photograph and invitation, undated (Box 56)
    - Vassar Weekly, undated (Box 56)
    - Tickets, 1915-1916, undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Music books, 1923, 1940; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Opera program, undated (Box 56)
    - One Act Play Magazine, 1937 December (Box 56)
    - Book of Names and exhibition catalogue, 1942 (Box 57)
    - Newspaper, pamphlet, notes, 1942 March 25 (Box 57)
    - Brochure of railroad, play booklet, Leaflet of the Authors' League Fellowship, booklet of The Coffee House, Play Book of Stewarts' "Rebound", theatre pamphlet, 1916-1921 undated (Box 57)
    - Map of Budapest, Lyrics to songs, 1918, undated (Box 57)
    - Theatre pamphlet, Church leaflet, notes, 1918, undated (Box 57)
    - Yale: miscellaneous, 1916 (Box 57)
    - Prayer books, 1894; 1915 (Box 57)
    - Biographical sketch, undated (Box 57)
    - 80th birthday celebrations, menu from Bentley's restaurant, London (Box 57)
    - 80th birthday celebrations, card and messages received, 1974 (Box 57)
    - 80th birthday celebrations, list of people attending Donald Ogden Stewart's party (Box 57)
    - Book list (Box 57)
    - Diary, 1972-1976 (Box 57)
    - Drawing of Donald Ogden Stewart by Patrick Woodcock, 1953 (Box 57)
    - The Exonian certificate of election as editor, 1909 January 9 (Box 57)
    - Ephemera related to films of Donald Ogden Stewart, undated (Box 57)
    - Photograph negatives of Frazzle Top Farm, Upper Jay, New York, 1950 (Box 57)
    - Sale of Frazzle Top Farm, undated (Box 57)
    - Interview with Donald Ogden Stewart, undated (Box 57)
    - Invitations, 1915, 1952, 1960 (Box 57)
    - Ledger, 1959-1961 (Box 57)
    - Legal Briefs, circa 1956 (Box 57)
    - Lists, miscellaneous (Box 57)
    - Print of Ohio Central Normal School, Worthington Ohio (Box 57)
    - Passes and Permits (Box 57)
    - Passports and passport photographs, 1930 and 1947 May 27 (Box 57)
    - Receipts, miscellaneous, 1951-1974 (Box 57)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 57)
    - Wills, 1941-1972, undated (Box 57)
    - Codicils, 1941-1973 (Box 57)
    - Lists of assets, 1958-1971 (Box 57)
    - Notes, undated (Box 57)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden, Junior
    - Hockey rule book, newspaper, The Harvard Advocate, Exeter Info., papers, clippings, notes, 1948-1949; 2 (Box 57)
    - Papers and photographs, 1950; undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Stewart, Gilbert Holland, Senior
    - Documents, 1865; 1894 (Box 57)
    - Documents of Army enlistment and diploma, 1898 October 23; 1903 June 17
  - Winter, Adolph. "Collection of English Songs," bound collection of printed music, with additional sheet music, fragments and notes, laid in., undated
  - Winter, Ella
    - Exams, miscellaneous notes and writing, Girl's Grammar School Notes, 1911-1914 (Box 58)
    - Stationary, undated (Box 58)
    - Lecture Notes, 1918 (Box 58)
    - Correspondence, clippings, notes, 1914-1921 (Box 58)
    - Library Book List, 1921 (Box 58)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 58)
    - Journal, 1924 (Box 58)
    - Day Planners, 1918-1949; 9 (Box 58)
    - Address Books, undated; 7 (Box 59)
    - Recipes, undated (Box 59)
    - Clippings, pamphlets regarding death of G.W.L. Marshall-Hall, 1914-1915 (Box 59)
    - Clippings, miscellaneous, 1922 (Box 59)
    - Calling cards, undated (Box 59)
    - Document, 1916 (Box 59)
    - Certificate and poster, 1933 (Box 59)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 59)
    - Book, 1944-1945 (Box 59)
    - Ephemera, undated; 7 (Box 59)
    - Maps in case, undated (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 3 (Box 59)
    - Notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 60)
    - German war script (money), 1919-1920 (Box 60)
    - Drawings on the back of menus, 1937 April 20-23 (Box 60)
    - Box (Box 60)
    - Maps, undated; 2 (Box 60)
    - Postcards, undated; 2 (Box 60)
    - Music books, 1900; 1916; undated; 5 folders (Box 60)
    - Notebook, notes, 1949; undated (Box 60)
    - Drawings, 1937; undated; 5 folders (Box 60)
    - Intelligence Test, Insurance Form, undated (Box 60)
    - Drawings, Photos, Clippings, relating to Ella Winter, 1948; undated (Box 60)
    - Business Cards, undated (Box 60)
    - Catalogue, undated (Box 60)
    - Pamphlets, 1932; 1949; 8 folders (Box 60)
    - "Diary of the Great Strike", 1926 (Box 60)
    - Clippings, 1945; undated (Box 60)
    - Magazine, notes, notebooks, 1947; undated (Box 60)
    - Notes, clippings, undated; 6 (Box 60)
    - Architectural drawing, undated (Box 60)
    - Pall Mall cigarette and note, undated (Box 60)
    - Wills, 1947-1960 (Box 60)
    - Codicils, 1967-1969 (Box 60)
    - Lists of assets, undated (Box 60)
    - Notes, undated (Box 60)
    - Poster of Ella Winter, undated
    - Scrapbook of political cartoons, undated
    - Clippings, undated
    - Map of U.S.A., undated
    - Drawings "Pläne zu einem Kulturhistorisches Museum", undated; 2
    - Print of "Venusfest", undated
    - Drawing, engravings, photographs, undated
    - Sculpture of shoe inscribed "Burillo '59", undated
  - Photographs
    - Donald Ogden Stewart, circa 1898-1940 (Box 61)
    - Portrait of Donald Ogden Stewart while at Yale University, undated
    - Portrait of Donald Ogden Stewart with members of Skull and Bones, undated
    - Donald Ogden Stewart's ancestors, undated (Box 61)
    - Donald Ogden Stewart, Philip Barry, and Ellen Semple on a steamer, and bullfight, circa 1924 (Box 61)
    - Ella Winter, Lincoln Steffens, Pete Steffens, Winter family, and others, circa 1924; 4 folders (Box 61)
    - Ella Winter, Pete Steffens, and others, 1940s (Box 61)
    - Ella Winter, Pete Steffens, California, and unidentified, undated; 4 (Box 61)
    - Portraits of Ella Winter, Lincoln Steffens with Pete Steffens, and Tony Sujam by Edward Weston, 1930
    - Ella Winter and Donald Ogden Stewart, circa 1955; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Portrait of Ella Winter and Donald Ogden Stewart at their home 103 Frognal, undated
    - Ella Winter and Donald Ogden Stewart at Peace Conference (Box 61)
    - Snapshots related to Ella Winter's writing projects and travels, undated (Box 61)
    - "Ames -- Philly, Temple, and Trip Across U.S.", 1949 (Box 61)
    - Portrait of Pete Steffens, undated (Box 61)
    - Portrait of Pete Steffens and students at Balliol College, Oxford University, 1951
    - Portraits and snapshots of Lincoln Steffens, George Bernard Shaw, Ezra Pound, Robinson Jeffers, Willard Johnson, Langston Hughes, undated (Box 61)
    - Portraits of Lincoln Steffens, undated; 3 (Box 61)
    - Portraits of Lincoln Steffens and ancestors, undated (Box 62)
    - Portraits of Lincoln Steffens and others, undated; 7 (Box 62)
    - Photographs relating to Steffens' book projects, 1898, undated
    - Portrait of Olympe Bradna, undated
    - Portrait of Jo Davidson, undated
    - Portrait of Katherine Hepburn, undated
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt and Max F. Schwittberger, 1908 May 21 and 1903
    - Portrait of Charles Erskine Scott Wood, 1932 (Box 62)
    - Photographs of art, undated; 2 (Box 62)
    - Stills from Joan of Arc with Ingrid Bergman, 1948 (Box 62)
    - Stills from Rebound, Stewart and wife, friends, undated
    - Stills from The Witches of Salem, undated (Box 62)
    - Unidentified portrait in frame, undated (Box 62)
    - Unidentified, undated; 2 (Box 62)
    - Unidentified actress, undated (Box 62)
- Financial Papers, 1909-1972; Series IV; 5.63 linear feet (6 boxes)
  The series contains various bank statements, bills, accounts, receipts, and correspondence with banks and lawyers pertaining to Stewart and Winter's personal finances. Royalty statements provide evidence of Stewart and Winter's livelihood as authors. The series also includes vital records, such as wills, and documents pertaining to various properties.
  - Ella Winter, stock papers, 1940-1941 (Box 63)
  - Letters from law offices to Ella Winter and Mrs. J. J. Hollister, 1935 (Box 63)
  - Tax forms of Ella Winter, J. L. Steffens, stock papers, royalty statements, 1926-1937 (Box 63)
  - Letters and receipts from the State Bank of the U.S.S.R. to Ella Winter, 1933-1936 (Box 63)
  - Ella Winter account records, undated; 3 (Box 63)
  - Ella Winter stock papers, 1941 (Box 63)
  - Royalty Statements, 1936 (Box 63)
  - Receipts, 1941; 3 (Box 63)
  - Royalty Statements, 1940-1941 (Box 63)
  - Letters from U.S.S.R., 1937 (Box 63)
  - Stock papers, 1937 (Box 63)
  - Tax papers, 1938-1941 (Box 63)
  - Royalty statement, 1941 (Box 63)
  - Bank statements, 1937-1938 (Box 63)
  - Bank records, 1936-1941 (Box 63)
  - Records of belongings, 1940 (Box 63)
  - Real estate records, 1937-1940 (Box 63)
  - Travel expense records, 1938 (Box 63)
  - Income tax forms, 1939, 1941; 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Laird, Bissell, and Meeds stock records, 1939-1940; 2 (Box 63)
  - Stock papers, 1937-1938; 2 (Box 63)
  - Estate papers, 1941; 2 (Box 63)
  - Bank deposit book, 1936-1941 (Box 63)
  - Insurance records, 1944-1948 (Box 64)
  - Insurance records, 1941-1943 (Box 64)
  - Insurance records, 1933-1944 (Box 64)
  - Insurance records, 1921-1933 (Box 64)
  - Deposit books, 1943-1944 (Box 64)
  - Receipt, 1941 (Box 64)
  - Stock records, 1942 (Box 64)
  - Bank book, 1929 (Box 64)
  - Bank records, 1940 (Box 64)
  - Bank records; miscellaneous, 1931; 2 (Box 64)
  - Notes; clippings, 1941 (Box 64)
  - Bank records; receipts, 1938-1944; 10 (Box 64)
  - Real estate taxes, 1928-1935 (Box 65)
  - Bank statements, 1930-1941; 8 (Box 65)
  - Checks, 1926-1931; 7 (Box 65)
  - Checks, 1926-1931; 5 (Box 66)
  - Bank statements, 1927 (Box 66)
  - Receipts, 1919-1921 (Box 66)
  - Ledgers, 1873-1935; 5 (Box 66)
  - Checkbook registers, 1927-1933; 7 (Box 66)
  - Checkbook registers, 1927-1933; 12 (Box 67)
  - Statements, 1933 (Box 67)
  - Checks, 1944 (Box 67)
  - Account Books, 1909; undated (Box 67)
  - Bank statements, 1934 (Box 67)
  - Bills, receipts, checks, journal, circa 1912-1931 (Box 67)
  - Contracts, agreements, leases, 1913-1948 (Box 67)
  - Income tax, 1929-1933; 5 (Box 67)
  - Insurance, 1926-1927 (Box 68)
  - Northwestern National Life Insurance Company: receipts, 1927-1936 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Banker's Trust Company, 1959-1967 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Bernard Reis & Company, 1957-1967, undated (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Crane & Hawkins, 1958-1959 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Herbert Oppenheimer, Nathan &Vandyke, 1967 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Katz, Charles J. attorney at law, 1955-1967, undated (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Pritchard Englefield & Company, 1962-1967 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with See, Denise, solicitor, 1957-1958 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence with Stuart D.D. Pearl, 1959 (Box 68)
  - Correspondence between family members regarding estates, 1958-1972, undated (Box 68)
- Oversize and Other Storage, 1.17 linear feet (14 boxes)
  - Bryan, Joseph, III (Series I), 1973-1974 (Box 69)
  - Keats, John [re: Dorothy Parker] (Series I), 1968-1971 (Box 69)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden (Series I), 1944-1958, undated (Box 69)
  - Williams, Marshall H. (Series I), 1974-1978 (Box 69)
  - Yale University (Series I), 1912-1921 (Box 69)
  - The Other Day (Series II), n.y. July 24 (Box 69)
  - Writings about comic books and related clippings (Series II), 1948; undated (Box 69)
  - Subject File: Capitalism (Series II), undated (Box 69)
  - Platt, David, "The Hollywood Witchunt of 1947," printed version (Series II), 1977 December (Box 69)
  - By a Stroke of Luck! scrapbook of photographs (Series II), Before 1975 (Box 70)
  - Honor Bright scrapbook (Series II), 1958 (Box 70)
  - The Kidders scrapbook of photographs (Series II), 1950 (Box 71)
  - The Kidders photograph of Arts Theatre Club (Series II), 1950 (Box 71)
  - The Kidders and How I Wonder posters (Series II), undated (Box 72)
  - Subject File: Charlie Chaplin (Series II), 1957-1967 (Box 72)
  - Posters for Congrès Mondial des Partisans de la Paix (Series III), 1949 April (Box 72)
  - Stewart, Gilbert Holland, Senior: Documents of Army enlistment and diploma (Series III), 1898 October 23; 1903 June 17 (Box 72)
  - Photographs: Donald Ogden Stewart in portrait with members of Skull and Bones (Series III), undated (Box 72)
  - The Carmel Pine Cone (Series II), 1934 February 16 (Box 73)
  - The Carmel Pine Cone (Series II), 1936 May 22; 1936 June 12-19; 1934 September 7 (Box 73)
  - The Carmel Pine Cone (Series II), 1931 May 22; 1934 August 10-31; 1936 May 22; 1934 January 26; 1935 May 24 (Box 73)
  - The Carmelite, Carmel Sun, The Californian (Series II), 1932 February 4; 1933 September 21; 1936 June 25 (Box 73)
  - Collier's (Series II), 1921 January 15; 1939 March 4 (Box 73)
  - Delineator (Series II), 1928 March, 1929 October (Box 73)
  - The Exonian (3 folders) (Series II), 1910-1912 (Box 74)
  - Hollywood Spectator (Series II), 1939 April 15 (Box 75)
  - The Hollywood Tribune (Series II), 1939 September 11, 18; 1939 August 14; 1939 May 19 (Box 75)
  - The Hollywood Tribune (Series II), 1939 July 10; 1939 July 3; 1939 June 23 (Box 75)
  - The Hollywood Tribune [2 copies] (Series II), 1939 June 23 (Box 75)
  - The Hollywood Tribune [11 copies] (Series II), 1939 September 18 (Box 75)
  - The Hollywood Tribune (Series II), 1939 June 2-16 (Box 75)
  - The Pacific Rural Press (Series II), 1934 September 15 (Box 75)
  - Pictorial Review (Series II), 1930 April (Box 75)
  - The Wasp (Series II), 1932 June 11 (Box 75)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 27 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 21-25 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 21; October 22; 1936 July 27 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 21 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 17-20 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 10-20 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 5-23; 1927 Dec 16; 1933 November 14-17 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 November 2-11; 1933 October 12-28 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1933 October 13-19; 1936 June 4-29; 1936 May 11 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1936 May 7-18; 1936 April 6-27; 1936 February 10-24; 1936 March 16 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1934 May 20; 1936 May 11-25; 1936 June 1-22; 1936 August 31 (Box 76)
  - Newspapers (Series II), 1909 September 15-1910 June 25 (Box 77)
  - Newspaper (Series II), 1959 June 27 (Box 77)
  - French magazine (Series II), 1931 December 16 (Box 77)
  - Russian magazines (4 folders) (Series II), 1930 (Box 77)
  - Diplomas, honor rolls, documents (Series III), 1906; undated (Box 78)
  - High School and college diplomas (Series III), 1912 June 24-1916 (Box 78)
  - Map of U.S.A. (Series III), undated (Box 78)
  - Drawings "Pläne zu einem Kulturhistorisches Museum" (Series III), undated; 2 (Box 78)
  - Print of "Venusfest" (Series III), undated (Box 78)
  - Drawing, engravings, photographs (Series III), undated (Box 78)
  - Drawing of Lincoln Steffens (Series III), undated (Box 78)
  - Scrapbook (Series III), 1913; undated (Box 79)
  - Poster of Ella Winter (Series III), undated (Box 79)
  - Scrapbook of political cartoons (Series III), undated (Box 79)
  - Clippings (Series III), undated (Box 79)
  - Photographs: Donald Ogden Stewart while at Yale University (Series III), undated (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Ella Winter, Lincoln Steffens with Pete Steffens, and Tony Sujam by Edward Weston (Series III), 1930 (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Jo Davidson (Series III), undated (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Katherine Hepburn (Series III), undated (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Theodore Roosevelt and Max F. Schwittberger (Series III), 1908 May 21 and 1903 (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Rebound, Stewart and wife, friends (Series III), undated (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Ella Winter and Donald Ogden Stewart at 103 Frognal (Series III), undated (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Pete Steffens and students at Balliol College, Oxford University (Series III), 1951 (Box 80)
  - Photographs: Lincoln Steffens (Series III), 1903-1904, undated; 6 folders (Box 81)
  - Photographs: Relating to Steffens' book projects (Series III), 1898, undated (Box 81)
  - Photographs: Olympe Bradna (Series III) (Box 81)
  - Winter, Adolph. "Collection of English Songs," bound collection of printed music, with additional sheet music, fragments and notes, laid in. (Series III), undated (Box 82)
  - Scrapbook (Series III), 1884-1912 (Box 83)
  - World War I scrapbook (Series III), 1914-1918
  - The Kidders poster (Series II), undated (Box BSD 84)
  - Sculpture of shoe inscribed "Burillo '59" (Series III), 1959 (Box 85)